Finding Aid for the Norman Cousins Papers LSC.1385
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Volume 3
  - Document Case # 388, 1964
    - 4. Folder. Correspondence - OU-OZ (Box 374a)
    - 5. Folder. Correspondence - PA-PD (Box 374a)
    - 6. Folder. Correspondence - The Ruth Paine Story (Box 374a)
    - 7. Folder. Correspondence - PE-PH (Box 374a)
  - Document Case # 389, 1964
    - 1. Folder. Correspondence - PI-PN (Box 376)
    - 2. Folder. Correspondence - PO-PT (Box 376)
    - 3. Folder. Correspondence - PU-PZ (Box 376)
    - 4. Folder. Correspondence - QU-QZ (Box 376)
    - 5. Folder. Correspondence - RA-RD (Box 376)
    - 6. Folder. Correspondence - RE-RH (Box 376)
    - 7. Folder. Correspondence - RI-RN (Box 376)
    - 8. Folder. Correspondence - Richmond, Va. Itinerary -, May 1, 1964 (Box 376)
    - 9. Folder. Correspondence - RO-RT (Box 376)
    - 10. Folder. Correspondence - Rochester, N.Y. Itinerary -, Jan. 7-8-9 (Box 376)
    - 11. Folder. Correspondence - RU-RZ (Box 376)
  - Document Case # 390, 1964
    - 1. Folder. Correspondence - SA-SD (Box 376)
    - 2. Folder. Correspondence - Schweitzer Hospital - Re: (Box 376)
    - 3. Folder. Correspondence - Saturday Review (Box 376)
    - 4. Folder. Correspondence - SE-SH (Box 376)
    - 5. Folder. Correspondence - Sands Point Country Day School (for the gifted child) - Lecture, April 24 (Box 376)
    - 6. Folder. Correspondence - Selinsgrove, Pa. - Susquehanna University -Lecture, April 27 (Box 376)
    - 7. Folder. Correspondence - ST-SN (Box 376)
  - Document Case # 391, 1964
    - 1. Folder. Correspondence - SO-ST (Box 376)
    - 2. Folder. Correspondence - SU-SZ (Box 376)
    - 3. Folder. Correspondence - Staff Memos (Box 376)
    - 4. Folder. Correspondence - Stone's Bi-Weekly (Box 376)
    - 5. Folder. Correspondence - Summerlane Camp (North Carolina) Controversy (Box 376)
  - Document Case # 392, 1964
    - 1. Folder. Correspondence - Library Associates- Brooklyn College- Distinguished Service Award Dinner (Box 376)
    - 2. Folder. Correspondence - T -Subscription Television Inc. (Box 376)
    - 3. Folder. Correspondence - TA-TD (Box 376)
    - 4. Folder. Correspondence - TI-TN (Box 376)
    - 5. Folder. Correspondence - TE-TH (Box 376)
    - 6. Folder. Correspondence - TO-TT (Box 376)
    - 7. Folder. Correspondence - TU-TZ (Box 376)
  - Document Case # 392, 1964
    - 8. Folder. Correspondence - UI-UN (Box 388)
    - 9. Folder. Correspondence - UO-UT (Box 388)
    - 10. Folder. Correspondence - U.N.A. of U.S.A. (Box 388)
  - Document Case # 393, 1964
    - 1. Folder. Correspondence - United World Federalists - N.Y. Metropolitan Comm. (Box 388)
    - 2. Folder. Correspondence - UWF - Pittsburgh PA. Dinner., May 7, 1964 (Box 388)
    - 3. Folder. Correspondence - UWF - Out-of-town (Box 388)
    - 4. Folder. Correspondence - UWF (Box 388)
    - 5. Folder. Correspondence - VA-VD (Box 388)
    - 6. Folder. Correspondence - VE-VH (Box 388)
    - 7. Folder. Correspondence - VI (Box 388)
    - 8. Folder. Correspondence - VO-VT (Box 388)
    - 9. Folder. Correspondence - WA-WD (Box 388)
  - Document Case # 394, 1964
    - 1. Folder. WE-WH (Box 388)
    - 2. Folder. Wharton, John - Lawyer (Box 388)
    - 3. Folder. WI-WN (Box 388)
    - 4. Folder. Winter, William " COMMENTS" (Box 388)
    - 5. Folder. WNDT - Channel 13 (Box 388)
  - Document Case # 395, 1964
    - 1. Folder. Correspondence - WO-WT (Box 388)
    - 2. Folder. Correspondence - WU-WZ (Box 388)
    - 3. Folder. Correspondence - XYZ (Box 388)
  - Miscellaneous Box -, 1940's
    - Clippings, articles, pamphlets, photos (Box 313)
      - 4. Clippings, Armed Forces (Box 313)
      - 5. Clippings, Aviation (Box 313)
  - Document Case # 396 Miscellaneous Box -, 1940's
    - Clippings, articles, pamphlets, photos
      - 1. Folder. Agriculture
      - 2. Folder. Anti-trust
      - 3. Folder. Anti-trust Wendell Berge
      - 4. Folder. Business
      - 5. Folder. Buyer's Strike
      - 6. Folder. Censorship
      - 7. Folder. Child Welfare
      - 8. Folder. C.E.D. & Dun & Bradstreet
      - 9. Folder. C.I.O. General
      - 10. Folder. Civil Libarties Union
      - 11. Folder. Communist Party
      - 12. Folder. Cooperatives
      - 13. Folder. Divorce
      - 14. Folder. Earthquakes
      - 15. Folder. Economy - General
  - Document Case # 397 Miscellaneous Box -, 1940's
    - Clippings, articles, pamphlets, photos
      - 1. Folder. Economy (Forecast)
      - 2. Folder. Employment - General
      - 3. Folder. Employment (Full)
      - 4. Folder. Fair Employment Practice Commission
      - 5. Folder. Famine Relief
      - 6. Folder. Finance
      - 7. Folder. Food
      - 8. Folder. Free Enterprise
      - 9. Folder. Health
      - 10. Folder. Housing
      - 11. Folder. Human Events
      - 12. Folder. Inflation
      - 13. Folder. Juvenile Delinquency
      - 14. Folder. Labor (Davis, William H.)
      - 15. Folder. Labor (General)
  - Document Case # 398 Miscellaneous Box -, 1940's
    - Clippings, articles, pamphlets, photos
      - 1. Folder. Labor - Guaranteed Annual Wage
      - 2. Folder. Labor - Industry Wide Coll. Barg.
      - 3. Folder. Labor - Misc.
      - 4. Folder. Labor - NLRB
      - 5. Folder. Labor - Wage Adjustment
      - 6. Folder. Labor - Women
      - 7. Folder. Liberal Party
      - 8. Folder. Magazine Analysis
      - 9. Folder. Medical Economics - A.M.A.
      - 10. Folder. Medical Economics - Correspondence
      - 11. Folder. Medical Economics - Dentistry
      - 12. Folder. Medical Economics - Deutsch, A. Clippings
      - 13. Folder. Medical Economics - General
      - 14. Folder. Medical Economics - Group Practice
  - Document Case # 399 Miscellaneous Box -, 1940's
    - Clippings, articles, pamphlets, photos
      - 1. Folder. Medical Economics (Hill-Burton 191)
      - 2. Folder. Medical Economics Labor & Industrial
      - 3. Folder. Medical Economics Legislation, Misc.
      - 4. Folder. Medical Economics Lists - Misc.
      - 5. Folder. Medical Economics Rural Medicine
      - 6. Folder. Medical Economics Voluntary Plans (Blue Cross Etc.)
      - 7. Folder. Medical Economics W-M-D Act - Social Security
      - 8. Folder. Medical Economics General I
      - 9. Folder. Medical Economics General II (Hearings & Bills)
      - 10. Folder. Medical Economics Medicine
      - 11. Folder. Medical Economics Mental Health
  - Document Case #400 Miscellaneous
    - 1. Folder. Ft. Ontario Refugee Camp. (Photographer - Nancy Clemens - 20 photos, more photos by misc. photographers) (Box 311)
    - 2. Folder. Medical Economics., (1 photo, view) (Box 311)
    - 3. Folder. USA Survey. (photos by Permanente Foundation) (Box 311)
    - 4. Folder. Vatican Going New Deal. (photos by Acme News Pictures) (Box 311)
    - 5. Folder. USA Ratings. (photos by Acme and United Artists) (Box 311)
    - 6. Folder. Rank of England. (empty) (Box 311)
    - 7. Folder. Pari-Mutuel. (empty) (Box 311)
    - 8. Folder. Photographs. (mostly of actors from various films) (Box 311)
    - 9. Folder. Football's Gravy Bowls. (photo) (Box 311)
    - 10. Folder. What it was Like - Atomic Bomb. (photos - Hanley) (Box 311)
    - 11. Folder. Night Clubs. (photos) (Box 311)
    - 12. Folder. Picture Oddities. (photos) (Box 311)
    - 13. Folder. Best Novel. (photos) (Box 311)
    - 14. Folder. Theater Stills. (photos of "State of the Union" - a play) (Box 311)
    - 15. Folder. Cover Picture. (empty envelope and typewritten sheet) (Box 311)
    - 16. Folder. Sidewalk Art - Helen Levitt. (Box 311)
    - 17. Folder. Unsorted. (miscellaneous stories) (Box 311)
    - 18. Folder. [UNK] Paintings. (photos) (Box 311)
    - 19. Folder. Mac Keuzukiver. (photos) (Box 311)
    - 20. Part of a magazine. (Box 311)
  - Document Case # 401
    - 1. Folder. Confidential - Scurry, Scurry & Pace - J.W. Rogers-, 1955
    - 2. Folder. Confidential - Miscellaneous -, 1955
    - 3. Folder. Confidential - Board of Directors: Minutes..., 1954-1956
    - 4. Folder. Lindsay, Jason -, 1958
    - 5. Folder. Father Conway -, 1957
    - 6. Folder. Everett, Glenn -, 1958
    - 7. Folder. Alcorn, Meade -, 1958
    - 8. Folder. Amring Article -, 1958
    - 9. Folder. Bibliography on Nuclear Weapons -, 1957-58
    - 10. Folder. Brown, Harrison -, 1958
    - 11. Folder. McKeldin, Gov. -, 1958
    - 12. Folder. Materials
  - Document Case # 402
    - 1. Folder. Check Books -, Pre- 1950
    - [UNK]. Folder. Confidential -, 1959
    - 2. Folder. Alston, Charlotte
    - 3. Folder.
    - 4. Folder. British Edition SR
    - 5. Folder. Globus, Rudolph
    - 6. Folder. Mehta, Ved
    - 7. Folder. Maremont, A.H.
    - 8. Folder. Nevas, Leo
    - 9. Folder. Paid Bills
    - 10. Folder. Paul, Weiss, Etc.
    - 11. Rogers, John Wm.
    - 12. Folder. Schur, Norman
    - 13. Folder. Silvermine Guild
    - 14. Folder. Teruaki
    - 15. Folder. Travel Refunds
    - 16. Folder. Whipple, Maurine
    - 17. Folder. WA-WD
    - 18. Folder. Wainwright Letters
    - 19. Folder. Walden, David (Fallout Suits)
  - Document Case # 403
    - 1. Folder- Confidential - - WE-WH, 1959
    - 2. Folder- Confidential - - WI-WN, 1959
    - 3. Folder- Confidential - - Wilson, Carroll, 1959
    - 4. Folder- Confidential - - Wilson, Mitchell, 1959
    - 5. Folder- Confidential - - Wittcoff, Ray, 1959
    - 6. Folder- Confidential - - WO-WT, 1959
    - 7. Folder- Confidential - - WU-WZ, 1959
    - 8. Folder- Confidential - - Y, 1959
    - 9. Folder- Confidential - - Z, 1959
  - Document Case # 404
    - 1. Folder. Confidentia l - State Department Report -, 1950
    - 2. Folder. E ncyclopedia Brittanic a Master Memo
    - 3. Folder. E.B.- Itinerary, Jan. 6, 1959
    - 4. Folder. E.B.-Agenda of April 7th Meeting-, 1959
    - 5. Folder. E.B.- Board Meeting - Chicago -, June 2-3-4
    - 6. Folder. E.B. - Minutes of the Meeting of April
    - 7. Folder. Itineraries -, 1958-59
    - 8. Folder. Board of Directors - S.R.- Conf., 1960
    - 9. Folder. Maremont, Arnold Conf., 1960
    - 10. Folder. Nevas, Leo Conf., 1960
    - 11. Folder. Gallagher Reports Conf., 1960
    - 12. Folder. Itineraries-, 1960
    - 13. Folder. Steinberg, Ellen -, 1960
    - 14. Folder. Travel Refunds -, 1960
    - 15. Folder. Investment Ideas -, 1960-1961
    - 16. Folder. Itineraries -, 1961-1962-1963
    - 17. Folder. Globus, R. -, 1961
    - 18. Folder. Maremont, A. -, 1961
    - 19. Folder. Ohio Farm -, 1961
    - 20. Folder. Silvermine Guild -, 1961
    - 21. Folder. Martin, Kings ley-, 1962
  - Document Case # 405 Amy Loveman & Neila Danielson (Danelius)
    - 1. Folder. Amy Loveman - Clippings
    - 2. Folder. Amy Loveman - (1) Letters About
    - 3. Folder. Amy Loveman - (2) Letters About
    - 4. Folder. Amy Loveman - Miscellaneous
    - 5. Miscellaneous Materials from Neila Danielius)
  - Document Case # 406 Neila Danielus Materials (Cont'd)
  - Document Case # 407 Miscellaneous -, 1963 - 1964- 1965- 1966
    - 1. Folder. American Freedom From Hunger -, 1963
    - 2. Folder. Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists -, 1963
    - 3. Folder. Civil Rights -, 1963
    - 4. Folder. Disarmament -, 1963
    - 5. Folder. Food -, 1963
    - 6. Folder. Hiroshima Peace Center Associates -, 1963
    - 7. Folder. Norman Hunt -, 1963
    - 8. Folder. Peace Action Center -, 1963
    - 9. Folder. Voice of Women, U.S.A. -, 1963
  - Document Case # 408
    - 1. Folder. War/Peace -, 1963
    - 2. Folder. Women Strike for Peace -, 1963
    - 3. Folder. World Law Fund -, 1963
    - 4. Folder. Nuclear Weapons
  - Document Case # 409
    - 1. Folder. Peace -, 1963
    - 2. Folder. Travel Expenses -, 1964
  - Document Case # 410
    - 1. Folder. SANE -, 1963
    - 2. Folder. SANE - Out-of-town -, 1963
    - 3. Folder. SANE - UWF -, 1964
    - 4. Folder. SANE - UWF Merger Discussion -, 1963/1964
    - 5. Folder. NC Memorandum for Proposed Merger of USUN and AAUN
  - Document Case # 411
    - 1. Folder. Thornton, Monte -, 1964
    - 2. Folder. Assorted Letters -, 1964-1965
    - 3. Folder. AAUN-USUN Merger -, 1965
    - 4. Folder. Bagels -, 1965
    - 5. Folder. "How To Write Without Thinking" - Letters to-the-Editor -, 1965
    - 6. Folder. Assorted Correspondence -, 1966
  - Document Case # 412
    - 1. Folder. U.S.I.A.- Nehru Project -, 1965
  - Document Case # 413 McCall Corporation - - Inter-Office Memos, Bd. of Dir. Meetings, etc., 1961-1967
    - 1. Folder. N.C. & S.R. Agreement -, 1961
    - 2. Folder., 1961
    - 3. Folder., 1962
    - 4. Folder. Mayes, Herbert -, 1962-63-64
    - 5. Folder. - ECom - Memos from Mary Harvey, 1963
    - 6. Folder. (con't) ECom from Mary Harvey, 1963
  - Document Case # 414 McCall Corporation (Con't) -, 1964 -1965
    - 1. Folder. ECom - Memos from Mary Harvey -, 1964
    - 2. Folder. Misc. Correspondence, financial reports
    - 3. Folder. ECom - Memos from Dori Lewis -, 1965
    - 4. Folder. McCall's Misc.
  - Document Case # 415, Dec. 1965
    Itinerary for Presidential Delegation to the Inauguration of President Marcos of the Philippines-
    - McCall's Financial Material
  - Document Case # 416 McCall's Memos (con't)
    - 1. Folder. Cor. with B-O-M CLUB
    - 2. Folder. McCall's Book Division - Harry N. Abrams -, 1966
    - 3. Folder. McCall's Magazine Critique - Confidential (unidentified -, 1966
    - 4. Folder. McCalls - Dayton
    - 5. Folder. Edelman, Robert - BOOK DIVISION
    - 6. Folder. Brennan, Francis
    - 7. Folder. Cominsky, J.R.
    - 8. Folder. ECOM budget - Confidential (Dori Lewis), 1966-
    - 9. Folder. Editorial Committee
  - Document Case # 417 McCall's Memos (con't)
    - 1. Folder. Educational Broadcasting Corp. - Re: Channel 13, 1966-
    - 2. Folder. Harcourt, Brace & World -, 1965-1966
    - 3. Folder. Mary Harvey -, 1966
    - 4. Folder. Langlie, Arthur & Williams, Harold
    - 5. Folder. Lewis, Dori, 1965-1966
    - 6. Folder. Mayes, Herbert R.
    - 7. Folder. McGraw-Hill, cor. with -, 1966
    - 8. Folder. Murphy, Arthur R., Jr.
    - 9. Folder. Murphy, Franklin D.
    - 10. Folder. Rich, Raymond A.
    - 11. Folder. Russell, Stella
    - 12. Folder. Simon, Norton
    - 13. Folder. Stein, Robert & Chassler, Sey
  - Document Case # 418, 1967
    - 1. Folder. National Educational Television (N.E.T.)
    - 2. Folder. N.E.T. Board
    - 3. Folder. N.E.T. Carnegie Commission Report
    - 4. Folder. (C.S.O.P.) Commission to Study the Organization of Peace
      (Research Affiliate of the United Nations Assoc. of the U.S.A.)
    - 5. Folder. Eichelberger, Clark - Board Meeting - UNA
    - 6. Folder. Educational Broadcasting Corporation
  - Document Case # 419, 1967
    - 1. Folder. SANE
    - 2. Folder. SANE - Mary Temple - "Negotiation Now!"
    - 3. Folder. SANE - Temple or "Negotiation Now!" - (Arthur Schlesinger)
    - 4. Folder. SANE - Correspondence
    - 5. Folder. SANE - Don Keyes
    - 6. Folder. SR Memoranda A-M
    - 7. Folder. SR Memoranda N-Z
    - 8. Folder. SR Staff Letters
    - 9. Folder. Ray Goodman Subscription Complaints
    - 10. Folder. UNA-USA
  - Document Case # 420, 1967
    - 1. Folder. Job Applicants
      - a- (DL position)
      - b- Female applications
      - c- Job applicants extraordinaire
      - d- Applications -Male
    - 2. Folder. UWF -, July 1967
    - 3. Folder. WAWF
      - a- Congress - Oslo, Norway, 7/30-8/5/67
      - b- Documents- Oslo
      - c- Misc. notes, Names-Oslo Congress
      - d- 57th Council Meeting- Oslo, July 30
      - e- Other resolutions
      - f- Oslo Declaration-, August 1967
      - g- Proposed and final WAWF Plan - Oslo, 1967
      - h- Who's Who at the WAWF Congress
      - i- Receipts - Oslo Trip
      - j- WAWF - William Sheehan
      - k- Information re: Yugoslavia, Bulgaria and on.
      - l- WAWF- Denmark-, August 1967
      - m- Letters re Grenville Clark (The Dag Hammarskjold Award)
  - Document Case # 421 Correspondence -, 1967
    - A -, 3 folders
      - Airlie House -, July 15
      - Amory, Cleveland
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies
    - B -, 1 folder
  - Document Case # 422
    - B -, 5 folders
  - Document Case # 423
    - 1. Folder. Beckmann, Dr. - Vietnam, Ionizers, Research Inst.
    - 2. Folder. Benton, William
    - 3. Folder. Balint, Nicholas
    - 4. Folder. Bowles, Chester
    - 5. Folder. Bruno, Father
    - F -, 3 folders
      - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies - Book Publisher's division
        Note: Correspondence starting with the letters C,D,E were never received.
  - Document Case # 424
    - G -, 3 folders
      - Gallagher Report
      - Greater New York Fund
    - H -, 1 folder
  - Document Case # 425
    - H -, 4 folders
  - Document Case # 426
    - Harvey, Mary
    - Hitzig Family
    - Horowitz, Bess
    - HPCA - Hiroshima Peace Center Associates
    - I -, 1 folder
      - International Book Institute
    - J -, 3 folders
      - Johnson Foundation (printed material)
      - Jovanovich, William
    - K -, 1 folder
  - Document Case # 427
    - K -, 3 folders
      - Kelly, Clay Mrs.
    - L -, 2 folders
  - Document Case # 428
    - L -, 2 folders
    - M -, 1 folder
      - March's Thesaurns
  - Document Case # 429
    - M -, 3 folders
      - Members of Congress for Peace through Law (Joan McKinney)
      - Members of Congress for Peace through Law (With Senators RF Kennedy & Clark) --"21", N.Y.C., May 23, 1967 (NC guest list included)
      - McA -McM
  - Document Case # 430
    - McN - McZ
    - McCalls
    - Magazine Publishers Association
    - Melman, Prof. Seymour
    - Mid dleton, Tom -- Double Crostics
    - unspecified, 2 folders Miscellaneous
    - N -, 1 folder
  - Document Case # 431
    - N -, 2 folders
      - NET -, 1967
    - O -, 1 folder
      - Organizing Committee for the International Book Institute (C.G.Benjamin)
      - Overseas Press Club and Bulletin
    - P -, 1 folder
  - Document Case # 432
    - P -, 2 folders
      - Paffrath, Leslie
      - P.E.N. (Poets - Essayists, Editors - Novelists)
      - Public Broadcast Laboratory- & PBL Policy Board, 1967
      - Publius Award Dinner -, 1967
    - Q -, 1 folder
    - R -, 1 Folder
  - Document Case # 433
    - R -, 3 folders
    - S -, 3 folders
  - Document Case # 434
    - S -, 3 folders
      - Schrag, Peter
      - Schweitzer, Albert, Re
      - SR Staff Memos
      - Special Report To Mayor John V. Lindsay, from Norman Cousins, Chairman, The Mayor's Task Force On Air Pollution -, May 9, 1967
  - Document Case # 435
    - T -, 3 folders
      - Thornton, Mrs. Monte
    - U -, 1 folder
      - Unidentified
      - University of Michigan - Sesquicentennial -, July 1967
    - V -, 1 folder
  - Document Case # 436
    - W -, 4 folders
      - Winters, Wm. Reports
  - Document Case # 437
    - Y -, 1 folder
    - Z -, 1 folder
    - DO-DR -, 1 folder
  - Correspondence - Document Case # 438, 1968
    - A -, 2 folders
      - American Heart Association On Ethics
      - Amory, Cleveland
      - Anti-Slavery Society - London, England
      - Applicants
      - Art and Adrenalin Letters
    - B -, 1 folder.
  - Document Case # 439
    - B -, 1 folder
      - Balint, Nicholas
      - BEM - Business Executives Move For Peace
    - C -, 4 folders
  - Document Case # 440
    - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions
    - Clark, Senator Joseph S.
    - Commission to Study the Organization of Peace
    - Cousins Family
    - Christmas Cards, lists received in 1968
    - Christmas Card s, Thank you's
    - Christmas gifts and thank you's
    - Cranston, Alan
  - Document Case # 441
    - D -, 5 folders
    - E -, 2 folders
  - Document Case # 442
    - F -, 1 folder
      - F - 4's
      - Family of Man
      - Father Bruno
      - unspecified, 2 folders
      - Ford Foundation
  - Document Case # 443
    - F -, 2 folders
    - G -, 4 folders
      - Gallagher Report
  - Document Case # 444
    - H -, 5 folders
      - Horowitz, Bess
      - HPCA
      - Human Rights Assembly
      - Human Rights Year
  - Document Case # 445
    - I -, 1 folder
      - INGO-- Earl Osborn
    - J -, 2 folders
      - Johnson Foundation (orinted material)
    - K -, 2 folders
  - Document Case # 446
    - K -, 1 folder
    - L -, 4 folders
  - Document Case # 447
    - M -, 2 folders
      - Mac-Mc -, 2 folders
      - McCall's -, 1 folder
  - Document Case # 448
    - M -, 1 folder
      - Middleton, Tom
    - N -, 2 folders
      - Negotiation Now!
      - Non-Proliferation -, 1968
      - Norway
      - [UNK] -, 1 folder
    - O -, 1 folder
  - Document Case # 449
    - O - Overseas Press Club
    - P -, 2 folders
      - Paffrath, Leslie
      - Pamfret, G.
      - Peacemakers Academy
    - Q -, 1 folder
    - R -, 2 folders
  - Document Case # 450
    - S -, 4 folders
  - Document Case # 451
    - S - SANE Newsletter
      - Schweitzer, Albert Fellowship
      - SR Staff Memoranda
      - Stone, I.F.
    - T -, 5 folders
      - Thomas, Norman - material re: taping made June 1968, 1930-32, 1951-63
      - Thornton, Mrs. Monte
    - U -, 1 folder
  - Document Case # 452
    - V -, 1 folder
    - W -, 4 folders
      - Wharton, John
      - World Assembly on Human Rights
  - Document Case # 453
    - W - World Association of World Federalists (WAWF)
    - Y -, 1 folder
    - Z -, 1 folder
  - Document Case # 454 Correspondence -, 1969
    - A
      - a-d -, 1 folder
      - e-h -, 1 folder
      - i-n -, 1 folder
      - o-t -, 1 folder
      - u-z -, 1 folder
      - Air Pollution -, 1 folder
  - Document Case # 455
    - B
      - a-d -, 1 folder
      - e-h -, 1 folder
      - i-n -, 1 folder
      - o-t -, 1 folder
      - u-z -, 1 folder
  - Document Case # 456
    - C
      - a-d -, 1 folder
      - e-h -, 1 folder
      - i-n -, 1 folder
      - o-t -, 1 folder
      - u-z -, 1 folder
  - Document Case # 457
    - Center for Inter-American Relations -, 1 folder
    - Commission to Study the Organization of Peace - 1 folder (Con't) in next case
    - Council on Foreign Relations -, 1 folder
    - D Center for Study of Democratic Institutions
    - Century Association
    - Christmas- e.g. cards, thank you's, gifts etc. -, 2 folders
  - Document Case # 458
    - C
      - Commission to Study the Organization of Peace-, 1 folder
      - Corporation for Public Broadcasting -, 1 folder
    - D
      - a-d -, 1 folder
      - e-h -, 1 folder
  - Document Case # 459
    - D (Con't)
      - i-n -, 1 folder
      - o-t -, 1 folder
      - u-z -, 1 folder
    - E
      - a-d -, 1 folder
      - e-h -, 1 folder
      - i-n -, 1 folder
      - o-t -, 1 folder
      - u-z -, 1 folder
  - Document Case # 460
    - F
      - a-d -, 1 folder
      - e-h -, 1 folder
      - i-n -, 1 folder
      - o-t - 1 folder (includes Friends of the Columbia Libraries)
      - u-z - 1 folder includes Fund for Education in World Order
  - Document Case # 461
    - G
      - a-d -, 1 folder
      - e-h -, 1 folder
      - i-n -, 1 folder
      - o-t -, 1 folder
      - u-z -, 1 folder
  - Document Case # 462
    - H
      - a-d -, 1 folder
      - e-h -, 1 folder
      - i-n -, 1 folder
      - O-t -, 1 folder
      - u-z -, 1 folder
  - Document Case # 463
    - I
      - India -, 1 folder
      - i-n -, 1 folder
      - International Peace Academy Committee-, 1 folder
      - o-t -, 1 folder
      - u-z -, 1 folder
      - Institute of International Education -
  - Document Case # 464
    - J
      - a-d -, 1 folder
      - e-h -, 1 folder
      - i-n -, 1 folder
      - o-t -, 1 folder
      - u-z -, 1 folder
    - K
      - a-d -, 1 folder
  - Document Case # 465
    - K (con't)
      - e-h -, 1 folder
      - i-n -, 1 folder
      - o-t -, 1 folder
      - u-z -, 1 folder
  - Document Case # 466
    - L
      - a-d -, 1 folder
      - e-h -, 1 folder
      - i-n -, 1 folder
      - o-t -, 1 folder
      - u-z -, 1 folder
    - M
      - a-d -, 1 folder
  - Document Case # 467
    - M (Cont.)
      - e-h -, 1 folder
      - i-n -, 1 folder
      - o-t -, 1 folder
      - u-z -, 1 folder
    - N
      - a-d -, 1 folder